<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ted Summer</title>
    <link>https://www.tedsummer.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ted Summer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>ted.summer2@google.com (Ted)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>ted.summer2@google.com (Ted)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 13:26:35 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.tedsummer.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>aws lambda: local server</title>
      <link>https://www.tedsummer.com/post/lambda-local/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 13:26:35 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>ted.summer2@google.com (Ted)</author>
      <guid>https://www.tedsummer.com/post/lambda-local/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been messing around with a project which uses netlify and lambda (it&amp;rsquo;s free and static sites are hawt). I basically have one main lambda function which handles api requests built in golang. It&amp;rsquo;s pretty awesome how easy netlify lets you build and deploy, but I wanted to a nice local setup for building and testing my api server. I think aws has its own tooling for this, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t really want to start fooling with it, so I came up with this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jq: looping</title>
      <link>https://www.tedsummer.com/post/jq-loop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 13:26:35 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>ted.summer2@google.com (Ted)</author>
      <guid>https://www.tedsummer.com/post/jq-loop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick example of using jq in a for loop. jq has some nice functional stuff built in such as &lt;code&gt;map()&lt;/code&gt;, but sometimes you need to do some fancy stuff with the data.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jq: group, unique, average</title>
      <link>https://www.tedsummer.com/post/jq-picoctf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 13:26:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>ted.summer2@google.com (Ted)</author>
      <guid>https://www.tedsummer.com/post/jq-picoctf/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve been running through &lt;a href=&#34;https://2018game.picoctf.com/&#34;&gt;picoCTF 2018&lt;/a&gt; and saw this problem that can be solved with some cool stuff from &lt;a href=&#34;https://stedolan.github.io/jq/&#34;&gt;jq&lt;/a&gt; (a handy JSON processor for the command line).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Question: What is the number of unique destination IPs a file is sent to, on average?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.tedsummer.com/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>ted.summer2@google.com (Ted)</author>
      <guid>https://www.tedsummer.com/page/about/</guid>
      <description> I currently live in Denver Colorado I enjoy  🧗‍♂️ climbing 🚲 cycling 🍌 eating bananas ✏️ drawing badly 🎶 music trying to do good     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.tedsummer.com/personal-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>ted.summer2@google.com (Ted)</author>
      <guid>https://www.tedsummer.com/personal-projects/</guid>
      <description>I like to build simple apps and tools. A 🏗 in the title indicates a work in progress.
🏗 liztz Vue A lightweight note taking application centered around lists.
🏗 GitHub Actions by Example GitHub Actions, Golang GitHub Actions by Example is an introduction to GitHub&amp;rsquo;s Actions and Workflows through annotated example YAML files. I wrote a custom HTML generator in Golang to generate the documentation from special YAML files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://www.tedsummer.com/page/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>ted.summer2@google.com (Ted)</author>
      <guid>https://www.tedsummer.com/page/resume/</guid>
      <description>Education M.S. in Computer Science University of Chicago, 3.9 / 4.0, 2018-2019
Relevant coursework:
Algorithms C Programming Operating Systems Networks Parallel Programming Big Data Application Security Intro to Computer Systems Discrete Math B.S. double major in Neuroscience and Chinese Studies Furman University, 3.48 / 4.0, 2012-2016
Work experience Senior Software Developer Devetry
September 2019 - Present
 Solving complex problems for clients with custom software and codebase improvements (Python, Django, Golang, JavaScript, XML Schema, PHP) Technical lead for the rebuilding of the Devetry website (Netlify, React)  Graduate Practicum Student, Developer University of Chicago - Globus Labs</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>https://www.tedsummer.com/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>ted.summer2@google.com (Ted)</author>
      <guid>https://www.tedsummer.com/talks/</guid>
      <description>Server-sent Events Presented at: Devetry Lunch and Learn
When: September 2020
Description: A brief introduction to server-sent events, when to use them and when not to use them.
Slides
Schematron Presented at: IBPSA: Guidelines and Projects for Building Data Exchange Integrity
When: August 2021
Description: Introduction to Schematron, a language for validating XML documents.
Slides</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>